[{
    "Question" :"What command do you use to commit using git?",
    "Answer" : "Git commit",
    "Topic": "Git"
},{
    "Question" :"What is a popular package manager used for a mac?",
    "Answer" : " Homebrew",
    "Topic": "General"
},{
    "Question" :"What does the linux command ls do?",
    "Answer" : "List files in current directory",
    "Topic": "Linux"
},{
    "Question" :"What OS is chocolatey used on??",
    "Answer" : "Windows",
    "Topic": "General"
},{
    "Question" :"What does mkdir do as a linux command?",
    "Answer" : "Make a directory",
    "Linux": "Git"
},{
    "Question" :"What is a docker container?",
    "Answer" : "A isolated enviroment for running an app",
    "Topic": "General"
},{
    "Question" :"How would you check your node version?",
    "Answer" : "node -v",
    "Topic": "Node"
},{
    "Question" :"What is docker?",
    "Answer" : "A platform for building running and shipping containers",
    "Topic": "Docker"
},{
    "Question" :"`Does linux use forward slashes or back slashes?",
    "Answer" : "Forward",
    "Topic": "Linux"
},{
    "Question" :"What does CD linux command do?",
    "Answer" : "Change directory",
    "Topic": "Linux"
},{
    "Question" :"What GIT command would you use to create a directory?",
    "Answer" : "Git init",
    "Topic": "Git"
},{
    "Question" :"What is GIT??",
    "Answer" : "A version control system",
    "Topic": "Git"
},{
    "Question" :"What is kubernetes used for?",
    "Answer" : "Application deployment",
    "Topic" : "Kubernetes"
},{
    "Question" :"What is the fastest way to find anything on a MAC?",
    "Answer" : "command + space",
    "Topic" : "General"
},{
    "Question" :"What is NPM?",
    "Answer" : "Node package manager",
    "Topic": "Node"
}]


